hi good morning this is how you can
register your account or your policy
number to the manual app app so download
the manual app app Google Play store or
App Store so once you have downloaded it
go to man left online. pH and
then
on register an
account to type in the email
address then the phone number
and uh the date of birth then click I
agree after that click
continue and then it will prompt you to
send an authentication code to your
email address or phone number so you can
choose whichever you are comfortable
with and then after you click it send
OTP the next thing that you need to do
is to set up your password just follow
follow the instructions and how to set
up and then you're good to go and then
you can sign in thank you